[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Hi, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "You're very famous now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "In your heart, what do you believe happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "He was trying to get home, and he was, and that's a fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "And you know that because you were talking to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "How often would you talk to Trayvon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "All day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "All day long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Yes, all day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "ORGAN: What kind of guy was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "He was a calm, chill, loving person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What would you talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Really, what we were going to be in life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "He was a good friend to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "A kind friend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Was he ever aggressive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Did you ever see him aggressive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Did he ever lose his temper?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "You mean the stuff on social media?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Did he ever talk to you about guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Did you ever see him with a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What about drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Drugs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Did he take a lot of weed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "How much would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Like twice a week.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Twice a week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Is that normal for teenagers in your community?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 113, "question": "You would do the same?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "No, because I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think they understood the world that you and Trayvon come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Don West gave you a very hard time, the defense attorney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Don West.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "What is your view of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I'm going to have to say, he -- like I'm a Christian.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Which is a dental condition for your teeth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "No, a bone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "You had to have surgery for it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Yes, I had to have surgery to push it back, and right now I don't want to do it, because it will take a year to heal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Have you been bullied for that before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Look at me, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Is that how you felt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "It's not that I didn't want to be there, it's a lot of stress.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "I was dealing with a lot of stress for 16 months, I think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "And you were grieving a friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Particularly the shocking fact that you were the last person he was talking to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Shock.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you miss him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What did you make of her testimony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I didn't think it was very credible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What do you feel about what that juror said about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Angry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What did that make you feel just seeing him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I'm holding back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "When she used the phrase creepy ass cracker, what did you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: I thought it was probably the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "And did you see that as a negative statement or a racial statement as the defense suggested?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I don't think it's really racial.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "What's your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, the juries, they see their fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "How do you spell it, first of all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Cracker.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "C-R-A-C-K-A?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Yes, and that's a person who act like they are police, who like (INAUDIBLE), who acting like, that's what I said to them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "And if George Zimmerman had done that, if he'd introduced himself as a neighborhood watch patrolman, even though he was off duty, if he'd done that, what would Trayvon have said to him, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "No, I'm just trying to get home.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "ORGAN: That was all he wanted to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", ",", "WDT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "When you heard the tape of George Zimmerman saying that these A-holes, these f-ing punks they're always getting away with it, before he has the confrontation with Trayvon, what did you think was going through George Zimmerman's mind when he said that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "I'm finally going to get one, that night.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "And be honest with me, Rachel, do you think that that was racially motivated or more a case of somebody he thought was a young thug, black or white?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "It was racial.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rachel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Do you think it was just wrong that you had no black people on the jury at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "No, not that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Would Trayvon, if he had been attacked or had been confronted, and he was scared, would he have whooped ass, as you put it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "EANTEL: Whoop ass.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Would he have defended himself if he'd been in that position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Yes, in my mind -- well, in reality, Trayvon, before his death, he thought I was still on the phone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "But you -- but you felt that there was no doubt in your mind from what Trayvon was telling you on the phone about the creepy ass cracka and so on, that he absolutely believed that George Zimmerman, this man, you didn't know who he was at the time, but this man, was pursuing him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "And he was freaked out by it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What was your reaction when you realized what she'd done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Look at the picture.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Do you feel that your testimony strongly impacted the case at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "In a negative way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Are you an honest person by nature?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes, well, now I'd be lying by saying that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "...in a serious trial?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "ORGAN: Well, what is your view of George Zimmerman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Weak, scary, hiding from his father.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Why do you say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "If you were a real man, you would have stand on that stage and tell what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Don"]}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Give evidence, you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Yes, I understand what Don's (ph) trying to say, oh, I switched it around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "So was there anything you wished you have said when you were in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Nigga.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "People -- the whole world say it's a racist word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "What does that word mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "That means a male.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "A black male?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "No, any kind of male.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Black or white?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Any kind -- Chinese could say nigga.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "And that's what they mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "They all say it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Because that's the racist word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 441, "question": "And they have just different meanings in -- in your community?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "No, in a generation...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "To young people, you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "...not young people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Did Trayvon have that in him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Do you think that she got an unfairly hard time in terms of the reaction to the evidence that she gave?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I believe she did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "So you don't think race played a role in this case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "I don't think it -- it did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ":", ":"], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What did you make of it, Cheney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I -- I couldn't hear your question so (ph)...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cheney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Did -- did you hear the interview I did with Rachel Jeantel, Trayvon Martin's friend just then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Yes, I -- I saw a part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["Rachel Jeantel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "I mean, do you think that justice has been done here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Well, I -- I think that -- that she clearly had -- could have done a better job testifying if she had been properly prepared by the lawyers, given an opportunity to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "What -- what do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Normal SOP.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "And as racial suggested, how much was the jury's decision affected by the fact that they were effectively an all-white jury?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "What -- what I know, Piers, is we don't know what somebody else thinks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "If she'd be more like that Rachel on the stand, could it have made a difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "LOW: Yes, I think it could have made a difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rachel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Is it the law that's the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "The law is the problem because the aggressor can then claim self-defense if the situation changes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jayne Weintraub"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", ":", "IN", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Do you think Florida or any other states will be making changes or modifications to the current stand-your- ground law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Jayne Weintraub, are we going to have a change to -- although stand-your-ground wasn't used in this case, it is prevalent in many states in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "Jayne?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "Our Constitution guarantees the defendant a jury of his peers -- not a victim, a jury of his peers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]